Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Everything okay?
-Would you get this dry-cleaned?
-Sure thing.
-Thanks.
You're amazing.
Thanks.
Let me see.
You got it!
You're a genius.
Thanks.
No sunflowers.
And divide them among the tables. Thanks.
-The kitchen's ready for you.
-Thanks.
-Yes! Thanks.
There's a sprinkler issue.
Help is on the way.
-How long?
-Five minutes.
-The awnings are out. Looks amazing.
-Right.
-It looks great.
-I know, right?
It looks fantastic.
Is that crooked?
-The big one?
-Yes.
No way. Lærke, everything's perfect.
This opening's going to be
completely smooth.
Oh boy, there's the boss.
Yup.
Wash this off before the VIPs arrive.
Of course. I'll get it done.
I'm trying to quit smoking.
Sit down.
No, everyone will be here soon.
We've got a selfie wall.
That'll occupy them for an hour. Sit.
Right.
I want to talk to you about something.
Listen.
So far we've bought
these rundown buildings,
renovated them,
put our logo on them, opened a hotel.
Beautiful. So proud.
But you've always wanted
to build something from scratch.
And Weltzer has finally agreed to do it,
and I've found a brilliant place.
It's in…
Málaga.
-Málaga?
-Yes.
There's a former mango farm owned
by a Dane. He's broke.
But he seems to be very attached
to the place.
For five years, the neighbors have tried
and failed to buy it.
That's where you come in.
I want you to go down there
and persuade him to sell.
Don't you have people for that?
I want you to do it.
It's always been your dream.
I want a seat on the board. So…
-When?
-Um… Now.
-What do you mean by "now"?
-Right now.
I can't do that. You know that.
-I'm going on vacation with Agnes.
-Bring Agnes.
-Stay a week.
-I promised we'd go to Bornholm.
You're being serious?
-Yes.
-Okay. It's just… Bornholm, really?
But she loves Bornholm.
I promised her.
Well…
-I'll do it after the vacation.
-But it has to be now.
I haven't taken a vacation in three years.
If I cancel again--
I want a seat on the board. The election's
in two weeks, so it has to be done now.
And Bornholm's not going anywhere,
unfortunately.
So go down there and soak it all in.
Do what you're best at. Right?
Yes.
You'll go there
and come up with a cool concept
and build the greatest hotel
Weltzer has ever put their name on.
This is your dream, Lærke.
What crappy weather!
Hi.
-How nice. Thank you.
-Thank you.
You're so frustrating!
Is she very upset?
It's just…
you can't just change the plans.
She was excited to hang out with you.
That's what we're doing.
That's cute, but it's not really, is it?
You'll be working.
-How will you hide it?
-You know what Joan's like.
I don't know what to do.
Yeah.
How's Vivi doing?
I have some news about Vivi?
Yes? She's dead?
Aw, she's dead,
and now you want me back.
We're pregnant.
She's pregnant. We're pregnant.
I'm going back on the school intranet.
With Vivi.
Yeah, it's tough, but it's also…
What can you do when you go younger,
you know?
Or not younger in that way. Not really.
-No more, please.
-No. Of course.
-Is she coming or what?
-Yes.
I need to tell you that she…
She didn't get into the school
of architecture. Sadly.
Wasn't the response due in August?
They start then.
The letter came two days ago--
Fuck!
She should have called me.
-She should have called?
-Damn!
I should have called her.
Damn, I should have.
You were working.
-I'm an idiot!
-A bit.
Never mind. When you get down there
and want to do something nice for her
because you're an idiot,
and you work a lot,
so you want to pamper her, and…
This is important.
Pay close attention.
No matter what, do not let her drive.
-Hi, sweetheart.
Right. Have a nice trip.
We'll be fine.
-Say hi to Vivi.
-Sure.
There's a door there. Bye.
Have a nice trip.
Love you.
Hi, sweetheart.
"Hi, Mom." "Hi, sweetheart."
-To the airport, please.
-Sure.
Dad told me about
the school of architecture. Sorry.
-Reapply next year. Lots of people do.
-I don't want to talk about it.
I thought the response was due
in August, that's why I didn't call, but…
Will you act like this
the entire vacation?
It's not a vacation! I'm not stupid!
-Excuse me?
-But--
I just wanted to ask.
This is my son, Elton.
He wants to see the plane take off,
but we got aisle seats.
Had you booked a window seat?
No, we didn't book window seats.
We got random seats.
Oh, that's a bummer.
Yeah. So…
I was hoping you might like to swap seats?
No, thank you.
-We're good.
-Okay?
Elton's only three,
and he's visiting his dad in Spain.
It's his first time flying,
so he's anxious.
But we've booked these, so no.
We've booked and paid for the seats.
-I don't care.
-No, stay there.
I said, "No." These are our seats.
Don't be sad, sweetie.
It might do him good
to be told "no" for once.
-Don't hit me!
-Have my seat.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
-Thank you!
-Don't mention it.
-So kind.
-Then all the kids get their way.
Yes, exactly. Thanks.
-Sure.
-We say "thank you" to the man.
What an annoying person.
You are so fucking unbelievable.
Me? She's the annoying one.
She should've booked seats.
It's not my fault…
-It's not my fault that--
-Shh!
-She could've booked--
-Do that one more time…
She could've booked her own tickets.
Set the iPad volume to maximum.
Should we get some food at the house?
And perhaps a glass of wine?
Where are we staying?
We're staying at a… finca.
That's a… Yeah.
I know what it is.
Right.
The owner's Danish,
and Joan arranged for us to stay there.
Someone she hooked up with?
I'm sure they've been screwing.
Ew!
What?
Don't say "screwing."
What? That's what it's called.
They actually screw…
a heck of a lot down here.
Lots of screwing, you know?
It's not my fault.
That's not my decision. But they do.
They love to screw,
especially in our area.
Is the word you don't like "screw"?
-Screwing here, screwing there
-Stop it!
Screwing in my tummy-- That's gross!
What are we doing?
Just checking something.
There we go. There.
What the hell is this?
That's this one.
Oh, right.
-I need to check something. Wanna come?
-No.
Fine. I'll be right back.
Jeez, it's hot here.
-Hi!
What are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
This is my place.
-This is your place?
-Yes.
Right.
I was told it was a former mango farm.
Orchard.
Got it.
This is our home,
and the orchard is up and running.
-Right.
-Yup.
What can I do for you?
It's really hot, isn't it?
Yes.
-I could do with a cold drink.
-Sure.
Have a seat on the couch.
I'll be right with you.
Right.
When it's your turn.
Yes, over there.
Okay. Thanks.
There you go.
What?
I've never seen
so many mango-based things before.
It's a mango orchard.
-There's a mangonade.
-No, it's pronounced mangonade.
Mangonade.
Like lemonade.
But with mangoes instead of lemons.
A mangonade?
-Want one?
-Yes.
-I've got to try it.
-Right.
Thanks.
Mangonade?
Jesus Christ.
Mangonade.
Do you have Wi-Fi?
Sure. We have 6G up here.
No, I guess not.
Never mind.
Hi. Can I help you?
Agnes.
Thanks.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's funny because
it's way too sweet and sticky,
and the glass is…
well, it's a disaster, but still…
it works.
It works. I'm impressed.
Wow. Okay.
-What?
-I've never heard anyone compliment--
-Was it a compliment?
-Yes.
And at the same time be so…
rude.
Isn't a compliment always nice regardless?
-Is it?
-I believe so.
You're cross-eyed.
Excuse me?
What?
Your eyes… You're cross-eyed.
No, I'm not.
And that's rude, by the way.
Yes, but it's very charming.
It's a compliment.
Okay.
Funny. Really funny.
Weltzer sent you, right?
Yes.
You've come a long way for nothing.
I've made it clear that I'm not selling.
Head back home
and sell some more waterfront houses.
-I'm not a real estate agent.
-You look like one.
You're rude. It's not nice to be here.
Oh, well. Seven.
-Seven?
-Euros for the mangonade.
No problem. Coming right up.
We only accept cash.
Weird that you don't have
more customers with that service.
-Lots of customers, but no change.
-Seriously?
Yes. Find something in our mango shop.
-No.
-Mango juice?
-No more mango. I've had enough.
-Dried mango?
-Definitely not.
-Mango jam?
-You know what?
-Mango vinegar?
It's not working, your mangonade.
And the name sucks.
-Mango beer?
-No, thank you.
-Mango chutney?
-No, thanks.
It's really good.
Fuck.
Agnes!
Oh, God.
Hi. Listen. My daughter wasn't in the car,
and I can't reach her.
-No reception.
-Your daughter?
Yes.
The girl from the plane?
-She's a big girl.
-I know, but--
-She probably just went for a walk.
-Where would she go?
Shit.
Paula?
-Are you there?
-What?
This is Paula.
Did you take a girl with you?
Yes.
You have to say "over"
when you're done speaking.
Over.
No problem, boss.
We'll be there in five.
Okay, thanks. It's fine.
-She's gone for a drive with Paula.
-Who the hell's Paula?
Paula's family.
It's fine. They're on their way back.
Is the fancy coffee only for fancy guests?
That hasn't worked for years.
Thanks.
Don't take it personally.
We just don't need more…
big, ugly hotels down here.
Fortunately, we don't build ugly hotels.
We have great taste.
You've got
really shitty reception here, huh?
Yeah. And we have
no running water at night
from 11:00 p.m.
to 7:00 a.m. every morning.
Inconvenient for watering trees.
Yes.
But fortunately all your friends
who have built hotels
by the water have water 24-7.
For their pools.
Got it.
-And Jacuzzis--
-My daughter's coming. I hear her.
Fountains.
Thanks for the coffee.
-Where the hell did you go?
-Just went for a ride.
You went for a ride.
You should've told me!
Is it funny?
-You acting like a mom?
-Funny.
-What are you doing?
-What's going on?
They're here to buy this place.
Dude, you always think
the worst of people.
It's the truth.
Do I have to worry about
where you are the entire time?
That's entirely up to you.
Is it 'cause we didn't go to Bornholm?
Are you punishing me for that?
Just drop me off at the airport then--
You're so childish.
Forget it!
Sit back.
Damn.
Agnes. Here. Take the key to the finca.
-I dunno know where it is.
-It says "Casa Dona" on the door.
-It's at the end of the street.
-They're stairs.
Bornholm has many stairs.
And The Sky Mountain and whatnot.
Crazy amount of stairs.
Want to order pizza?
I'm not hungry.
What? Come on. We haven't eaten all day.
-I'm not hungry.
-How about burgers then?
I'm going to bed.
Fries?
Or maybe some yummy pasta?
I'm going to bed.
Goodnight.
THANKS FOR THE WINE.
I'VE LOOKED AT THE PROPERTY. CAN YOU TALK?
SENT TO: JOAN
LET'S TALK TOMORROW
HOPE YOU HAD A GOOD FLIGHT. OUR BEEF
WELLINGTON GOT FIVE STARS. KRISTIAN
Agnes?
GONE TO TOWN, SEE YOU LATER.
P.S. THE BALCONIES ON THE HOTEL NEED
TO BE STAGGERED FOR VARIATION AND RHYTHM!
Hi. I thought you quit smoking?
Yes, right.
So, what did you think of the place?
The farm is still running.
What do you mean?
Well, it's a mango farm
or mango orchard,
as he calls it.
We'll tear it down.
There's water and electricity, yeah?
How's the internet?
It's kind of non-existent,
but that's practicalities.
We'll fix that.
The problem's the owner.
He's annoying, and refuses to sell.
Focus on the goal.
Get to know him and persuade him.
That's what you do.
Yes, but it'll take longer than you want.
-He's very--
-Are you with me or not?
-We have a plan.
-Yes, of course.
The board meeting is in 12 days.
You'll find a way.
-Yes.
-Ready, Joan?
-Gotta go. Call if you need me.
-I'll figure it out.
-I believe in you. Bye, sweetie.
-Bye.
We have a deal.
I'll pick it up next week.
Sure. See you later.
See you.
Are you serious?
Hey, beautiful. What?
-We need the money, beautiful.
-But we also need the mangoes.
Yeah, but I spoke to Hernando, and...
We can use some
of his coches for the harvest.
What?
I don't know.
I just feel like
I'm swimming upstream all the time.
Don't you ever get tired of…
swimming and swimming and…
and nothing?
Excuse me.
Where are you going?
Taking the Danish girl for a ride.
-Dude.
-"Dude." What?
We can't trust them, okay?
You can't be trusted.
-Yes, you!
-Me?
Nice shirt.
Thanks, sweetheart.
Cross-eyed.
-Shit! Jesus Christ.
-Hi.
Hi.
Who was that?
Carlos and Dimitri.
They own that hotel up there.
Nice shirt. What did they want?
-What did they want?
-Yes.
The same as you. They've been trying
to buy me out for the past five years.
-Would you show me around?
-Show you around?
-No, we need to start harvesting.
-What were you doing in Copenhagen?
-I told you.
-Come on.
Nobody travels for four hours
to turn down an offer.
Why did you go?
I had a meeting with the bank
about a loan extension.
They didn't grant it?
-No.
-How much do you owe?
We just need to bring in the harvest.
I don't get you.
I've been pretty clear.
Okay? It's not for sale--
What will you do?
-I'll figure it out.
-No, you won't.
You think this is a gold mine. It's not.
It's a run-down mango farm.
-Orchard.
-Orchard. Whatever.
You owe 4.9 million kroner.
You have no savings and no assets.
What's your plan?
The plan is for me to work
and for you to go home.
Okay?
Thanks for stopping by.
I'll just go down here.
Hopefully, I won't fall
down the steep slope.
A quick tour.
Come on.
Nice, huh?
Yes.
This place is…
magical with that view
and the constant northwesterly breeze
carrying the scent of--
The scent of mangonade.
We're here.
Right. Yes.
Thanks.
This is the heart of the orchard.
You've got the river that runs past
the house and down to the fields.
All right?
-When are they ready?
-Now.
They bloom in the spring around April,
and they're ripe now.
-Good morning.
It's not good.
It takes six to ten years
for a tree to produce mangoes.
-Hi.
-Hi, boss.
All right?
Was this always your dream?
Yes.
I've dreamed of starting a mango orchard
in Frigiliana since I was five.
Really?
No, you haven't.
What was your job?
I was a lawyer.
A lawyer?
Yes.
Oh. Why did you stop?
Was it love?
It's not too bad.
So it was love
and then you two started a mango farm?
-Orchard.
No, it…
belonged to her family.
-I have to work.
-Yes.
Can you find your own way back?
-Really?
-Left, right, left, and down the path.
On the ATV?
No!
But it's a really nice walk.
Still here?
Have a seat.
What if they can co-exist?
-What can co-exist?
-Your mango f…
-Orchard.
-…orchard and Weltzer's hotel?
Just… Okay.
If we preserve the fields,
the culture, and the trees.
The hotel guests would love it.
The hotel would bring life to the area
and create new jobs.
Your staff would keep their jobs,
you'd keep the place,
Weltzer would be happy.
They'll pump money--
You know there's no phone signal, right?
I did notice that. I just think--
Half the day, we don't have electricity.
Yes.
-No water at night.
-We'll fix it. Listen.
If we solve the infrastructure issues,
this would be mutually beneficial.
Right?
More activity, more jobs.
Well? It's not completely stupid, right?
Up, down, to the front, and inside!
OWNERS DIE IN DEADLY FIRE
LOCAL MANGO FARM DESTROYED
BY FIRE - BOTH OWNERS KILLED
DANE SAVES GIRL FROM FIRE.
THE ONLY TWO TO SURVIVE.
Before you freak out, I just want to say…
Want some?
Good, right?
Yes.
How was your day?
Really nice, actually.
-Really?
-Really.
Paula introduced me to one of her friends.
Then we went to a water park.
-Not like kids. More like--
-No. Not like kids.
Well, it actually was pretty childish.
-That sounds lovely, sweetheart.
-It was.
How about you?
I went to the orchard again.
So my legs hurt.
Why go back?
To find a way to build
that hotel for Weltzer.
I saw your drawings.
-Thanks for your input.
-You're welcome.
But I doubt you'll get them to leave.
Yeah.
We've been invited to a party down there.
No.
I bet it's a mango party, right?
Yes, I think it is.
A fucking mango party.
I'm sorry, I didn't know you got rejected.
-Fuck it. It doesn't matter.
-No.
It doesn't matter.
It does matter.
There's just been a lot going on lately.
Right.
-What?
-Nothing.
No, tell me. What?
A lot going on lately?
Like, the past 18 years, or what?
Do you remember your grandparents?
Dad's mom and dad? Yes, I do.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
Your dad's parents, but not my parents.
I got something when I turned nine.
I got a sticky note saying
they had gone to Munich,
and they put me up with our neighbors,
and came back for me a week later.
Well, it's not…
I mean, it's no excuse.
But I'm just trying to say I…
Your dad loves this kind of stuff.
And he's so good at it.
He's great at…
Christmas, lunch boxes, and homework.
And his parents--
When I picked you up, I felt I was…
tearing you away from your real family
and bringing you to a miserable apartment,
where you'd scream for him--
So it's my fault?
No. It's not.
I'm just saying that you had everything
at your dad's.
At my place…
there wasn't really anything at all.
My mom was there.
Yes.
I'm sorry. That's so lousy--
No, don't apologize.
-That's shitty of--
-No, I hear you.
I hear you.
It's the weekend. Aren't you going…
out with your new friends?
No, I think they…
They were tired and went home.
-You can always wine up your mom then.
-Yeah.
Paulita, give me a hand.
Coming.
-Are those from the southern end?
-Yes.
Do you think we'll be able to use them
for the harvest party?
I don't know.
Did you invite the Danes?
Yes, I invited Agnes.
What?
Dude, no way!
-Yes, way.
-No!
-Yes!
-Please.
I saw you all fancy in your new shirt.
Of course you don't.
Alex?
Yes?
I wouldn't mind.
I'm sure my sister wouldn't mind either.
Actually, I'm sure
she'd be happy about it.
What if both can co-exist?
The mango orchard and Weltzer's hotel?
If we preserve the fields,
the trees and the culture.
The hotel guests would really love it,
the hotel would revive the area
and create more jobs for the locals,
and we can build up trust
while we're expanding.
Anyway, I just wanted your opinion.
Call me.
Bye.
What are you looking at?
-What's up?
-What?
Why don't you just ditch Joan?
You're always making them money
and doing everything for them.
If you spent a fraction of that energy--
Didn't you want to be an architect?
Or was it a financial adviser?
I'm my father's daughter, right?
-Yeah.
-Talk to Dad about it.
He would help you.
-With what?
-Starting your own business.
No, I'm not going solo.
Not when I'm on my way up--
Stop! You have no boyfriend or friends,
you don't spend time with your family.
-What more do you need?
-I think I have plenty of friends.
When was your last boyfriend?
When?
Yes, when?
I don't want to discuss that with you.
Just tell me!
When was it?
-Dad?
-Yes. It was Dad.
Yes. Your phone's ringing.
Too bad.
I don't mean to be a bitch. Just saying…
My hands are wet. I can't.
I do have friends.
Hola, Paula.
Want to drive?
Really?
Yeah.
I don't get why Dad won't let me.
I crashed his car like twice.
-And then I'm banned for life.
-I'll just back it out.
I know how to.
I'll do it.
-Stop.
-Really good.
-Get your hand off.
-Great.
-Stay in your own lane.
-I am.
Yes, you are, but do it a bit more.
-But I'm in the--
-Like that. This is fine.
Am I cross-eyed?
-What?
-Am I cross-eyed?
Look at me properly.
What the hell are you doing?
Learn to drive, girl!
-Can you drive?
-It's fine.
Look forward--
-I am.
-Eyes on the road. On the road.
If you can drive here, then…
then you can drive anywhere.
Hi, Joan.
Bad connection.
Let me just get inside.
What did you say?
I just heard your message.
What's going on?
Do as you were told.
Forget about the local community
and mango orchards.
The board meeting's coming up
and this can't fail.
You were supposed to convince him
and make him sign--
Could you keep an open mind?
Couldn't we try to maybe--
Close the deal,
so we can tear down the mango farm.
-Hello?
-I gotta go.
-Bye.
-Hi.
I think there's a…
Yeah, push.
It's…
Are you coming?
Yes, all right. Yes, I'm coming.
Jeez, it's hot.
What's up, people?
Holy Mary, we've eaten so many mangoes,
we'll be sick to our stomachs!
-What a party, right?
-Yes!
Paula, I love you, beautiful.
Here we go.
I want to take a moment to talk
about a great friend of mine.
A friend who looks out for all of us.
Oh, Juan is at it.
I have to tell you something.
-Yes?
-If you've got a minute before.
-Sure.
-Alex?
Alex, Alex, Alex!
I gotta go make a fool of myself now.
No problem.
-We'll talk after.
-Yes.
-Grab a beer.
-Sure.
Alex, Alex, Alex!
Go, Alex, Go!
It's a pleasure to have you all here.
And I am certain
that Ría, Manuel, and Mari
would enjoy this very much.
Mari especially would enjoy
hearing my clumsy Spanish.
You?
This community is my family.
How do you say it, "Celebramos"?
-Celebramos!
A beer, please.
-Cheers.
-What did you--
-What--
You go first.
I liked your speech.
Thanks.
I didn't mean any of it.
What did you want to talk about?
Nothing.
It's not important.
You really don't speak Spanish?
You never picked it up?
I think that was pretty good Spanish
that I was just speaking.
I think I speak it pretty well.
-Hola.
-Hola, beautiful! I have to…
Yes, of course.
Hola? What's up?
Coming.
Hi.
Hi. What's up?
She's fine.
-Yeah?
-The girls were…
Or… they've had too much.
Are you okay?
-She's fine.
-Are you okay?
There's something on your face.
Come on, upstairs!
-You got her?
-Come on.
Get up. Get some sleep.
-I can't…
-No, get up! Sweetie.
-Okay.
-Grab her.
Yes. Where's she going?
Upstairs.
-All right.
-Mind your head.
It's the door back there.
Right.
-There.
-Got her?
Yes. There, sweetie.
Let's get her shoes off.
There, there.
Thanks.
A glass of wine?
Yes, please.
-Were they on the plane?
-Yes. But--
They were on the plane?
Yes, they were on the plane.
On a real plane?
Yes. A small one.
-No!
-Yes.
A small plane?
And they weren't…
I mean, they weren't going to take off.
-It was definitely Paula's idea--
-It wasn't.
I promise--
I'll bet it was my--
-No.
-Definitely!
Listen.
Paula thinks it's a secret,
but she wants to become a pilot.
So it was Paula.
Okay.
-I doubt it.
-She told me about her project.
Project?
Yeah, the one rejected
from the application.
-She told you about that?
-Yes.
It would've probably made more sense
if she hadn't had half a bottle of rum--
-Yes, I'm sure.
-But she's clever.
Really clever.
No wonder you're proud of her.
She hasn't told me anything.
About the project.
I don't really know anything
about it, but I…
haven't exactly asked either.
-What about you?
-What about me?
-What do you want?
-Me?
What's your big dream?
It's a big question.
No idea. I haven't thought about it since…
Since the fire?
I remember that…
I felt like…
everything had been taken away from me.
Everything I had,
everything I loved,
everything I believed in
was taken away from me in a split second.
But then I looked at Paula.
This little, precious girl, who…
She'd lost everything.
So I think I just…
I started rebuilding the farm,
and I took care of her.
And time passed.
And here we are.
Do you even like mangoes?
No. They're too sweet.
-They are too sweet.
-Way too sweet.
Lærke?
JOAN ZEUTHEN
MISSED CALL
HOW'S OUR PLAN WORKING OUT?
HAVE YOU PERSUADED HIM TO SIGN?
I think I might just take the day off.
Perhaps we could go
to that market you suggested?
If you want to?
You have a text message.
So that was your plan all along?
I didn't know how to tell you.
I understand why Agnes finds it
difficult to share stuff with you.
Tell her
she's always welcome at our place.
Have a safe trip.
Mom?
Hi, sweetie.
Are you okay?
We all do stupid things
when we like someone.
-Admit that you like him.
-No.
-Say it. You need to do it.
-Stop.
You always need to be
in control of everything.
It's not about whether I like him or not.
What's it about then?
I'm just not relationship material.
I'm the type you need to avoid.
I don't make people happy.
I've seen it.
He looks very happy.
Yeah.
And if anyone can solve problems,
it's you.
And you know it.
And no matter what…
you've given me
one of the best vacations I've ever had.
And you've definitely made me happy.
Hola.
Excuse me?
No, forget it.
No, that's my seat,
and your bag's in my seat.
Thank you.
-Thank you very much.
-Sure.
-Hi.
Didn't you have a baby?
-What?
-You had a baby with you?
Oh, right. He's with his dad in Spain.
Half Spanish, half Danish.
-Interesting.
-Yeah.
It can work out.
What's up with you?
Nothing.
Doesn't seem like it.
Can you relax a bit?
You haven't stopped all morning.
Can you talk to me?
Dammit!
Alex!
Alex.
Tired, you know?
And?
Were you talking about me or you?
You, obviously.
Look at yourself, you look super old.
Are you?
Yes, of course.
I'm gonna eat.
Hi, gorgeous.
What's up?
The board sent them.
I think we nailed it.
But he wouldn't sign it.
I got the contract this morning.
I don't know what you did. It's amazing.
He signed.
We just need the final documents,
and then you're off to Málaga.
It'll be sorted in a couple of weeks,
then you'll zip down there,
tear it all down,
build everything, decorate,
train the staff, and open.
Right.
I have to go.
But…
TRIED CALLING. LEFT A MESSAGE.
CALL ME. YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND…
LET ME EXPLAIN.
IT WAS A WONDERFUL NIGHT. SORRY.
-Hi there.
Hi.
I've read the applications.
They're impeccable.
Everything's by the book.
We can't contest a single thing.
-May I?
-Sure.
Where was I?
I talked to the bank.
Your friend owes them 4.9 million kroner.
Unless he can conjure up the money,
he has little chance of keeping the farm.
Yeah. Right, I've said it. That was all.
Thanks for trying.
Sure. All good.
How is she?
I think she misses you.
No.
She probably just misses Málaga.
Yeah, that too.
I think she misses you too.
Did you always breathe so heavily?
What?
Your breathing's heavy.
Stop it. It's annoying.
I can't stop breathing.
I breathe normally.
You're wheezing.
Okay. Listen. We're having a…
gender…
re… reveal.
You're having a what?
-We're having a--
-A what?
…gender reveal.
A baby shower, kind of… I guess.
A gender reveal?
Baby shower? Really?
Vivi really wants one.
-She does?
-Yes.
-Do you want to come?
-No.
-For Agnes' sake?
For Agnes and for me,
and just very briefly?
Thanks.
I can tell. Thanks.
Can I have the bottle?
It's Vivi, you know.
It'd be nice for her
just to have one glass.
Just take it.
Thanks.
By the way,
he has a 14-day withdrawal period,
if need be.
Okay?
-See you.
-Thanks for helping.
Gender.
SHOULD WE SELL YOUR HOUSE TOO?
APPRAISAL FREE OF CHARGE SOLD!
Three, two, one!
That was perfect.
Another little girl.
Awesome.
Please, dig in.
Are you snooping?
No. I'm not. Um…
Is that your project?
Yes.
it is.
How does it work?
-You don't have to ask.
-But I'd like to know.
-You know what tiny houses are, don't you?
-Yes.
So, everyone's got their own household.
And then you share the big expenses,
such as…
solar panels,
geothermal heating or wind,
depending on where you live.
Shared water supply and heating system.
The houses are, of course,
built from biogenic materials.
Preferably regenerative.
The walls are made of rammed clay soil
and insulated with seagrass,
and there's shingle roofs
made from wood scraps to make it
dynamic and environmentally friendly and…
What?
It's just a great idea.
And it's yours.
Thanks.
Tell the school of architecture that.
Fuck that school.
Yeah.
Fuck it.
Have you talked to Paula?
-Yeah. We've been texting.
-Yeah?
Have you talked to Alex?
Um… no.
I think the reception's quite bad.
Just call him.
There's cake.
Right. I'll be right down.
Agnes!
Come here, please.
What's up?
Pack your bag.
Are you stupid?
Yes, maybe.
-We'll build without you.
-You won't build that hotel.
Perhaps somewhere else, but not…
not in that orchard.
What can you do?
-We have a contract. He signed.
-But he has 14 days to cancel.
So you want to stop this?
You don't have to understand.
I'm grateful for everything.
I'm so sorry,
but this is the way it has to be.
I have to do this.
You're fired.
Yes.
Shit!
Good, and you?
Why are you here?
Can we talk?
-There's nothing to talk about.
-Five minutes and I'll let you be.
I have to bring in the harvest.
And we have nothing to talk about. Okay?
Fine.
Yeah.
They'll be fine.
-Are we done?
-Yes.
-Can we talk now?
-We have to move all the crates.
Help me.
Thank you.
Come on.
We're just standing here. Listen.
I'm working.
It's not insulin, it's mangoes.
Please just hear me out?
-What--
-It's diffi--
Then tell me!
It's difficult to apologize
when I'm yelling at you.
But I'm sorry!
I'm sorry I didn't do better.
I tried, but it went so wrong.
You did great.
You got what you wanted.
You've bought the place.
You'll get your shiny hotel. It's perfect.
Why are you here?
Because of you.
I'm here because of you.
You don't need to sell to Weltzer.
-What?
-I've sold my apartment.
And I've borrowed some money.
Quite a lot of money, actually.
Way too much money.
You've sold your apartment?
Yes.
You have huge debts.
Yeah.
You have no assets?
Nope.
What's your plan?
12 MONTHS LATER
Dude!
-Beautiful.
-Hi.
Hola, chica.
It looks pretty good, huh?
You look pretty good.
Are you proud?
Yes. Very.
-Are you crying?
-What?
-Am I crying? No way!
Are you so proud that you're crying?
-Just a little?
-No.
Let me see.
-Wet eyes--
-It's sweat.
-Eye sweat--
-I'm sweating.
-We need to talk about something.
-Okay?
Mangonade can't be on the menu.
Nobody gets it!
Everybody gets it once you explain it.
-Lemonade, mangonade.
-But--
We're also adding avocade.
-What? No.
-Avocade.
From avocado. So it'll be
lemonade, mangonade, avocade. Wow.
Great idea, right?
That will never happen!
Subtitle translation by:
Toke Lasvill-Andersen